//array for questions , options and numbers & answers
 let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "When is world science day celebrated ?",
        answer: "November 10",
        options: [
            "November 18",
            "November 10",
            "January 07",
            "March 07",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Which year is the first world science day celebrated ?",
        answer: "November 10, 2002",
        options: [
            "November 10, 2002",
            "November 10, 2001",
            "November 10, 2003",
            "November 18, 2003",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Who established the world science day ?",
        answer: "UNESCO",
        options: [
            "UNESCO",
            "World Health Organization",
            "CISCO",
            "NASA LAB",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "Why is world science day celebrated ?",
        answer: "Promote national and international solidarity.",
        options: [
            "To draw attention to the challenges faced by science.",
            "Promote national and international solidarity.",
            "Improve Science & Technology.",
            "Strengthen public awareness on role of Science.",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "What is the theme of the world science day for 2019 ?",
        answer: "Open Science, leaving no one behind.",
        options: [
            "Due to struglling with Covi-19.",
            "Human Right.",
            "Towards green societies.",
            "Open Science, leaving no one behind.",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "Science day is celebrated in India to Honour:",
        answer: "Sir CV Raman",
        options: [
            "Sir CV Raman",
            "C.P. Srinivasa Ramanujan",
            "Homi J. Bhabha",
            "Jagadish Chandra bose",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "Sir C.V. Raman awarded Nobel Prize on ... was a First Asian person.",
        answer: "1930",
        options: [
            "1956",
            "1933",
            "1930",
            "1935",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "UNESCO Headquarter is located in ?",
        answer: "Paris, France.",
        options: [
            "Geneva, Swizerland.",
            "Washington, USA.",
            "London, England.",
            "Paris, France.",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "Who invented Zero ?",
        answer: "Aarya Bhatta.",
        options: [
            "Aarya Bhatta.",
            "BrahamaGupta.",
            "Maharshi Walmik.",
            "Issac Newton.",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "Who invented Black Hole Theory ?",
        answer: "Stephen Hawking.",
        options: [
            "Issac Newton.",
            "Stephen Hawking.",
            "Bohr & Frontland Lab.",
            "None of Above.",
        ]
    },
 ];